<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Trails</string>
  <string name="draggable_button">Mobile Community</string>
  <string name="camp_info_1"> 1. Jemez National Forrest ($10 A Night)

    For campground inquiries, please call: (575) 829-3535
Season Dates

    Jemez Falls Campground facility is open during the following season(s):
•	May 15, 2020 – September 14, 2020 (Peak Season)

Overview

    Jemez Falls Campground is located in a stunning Ponderosa Pine and forest meadow environment. The campground elevation is 7,880 feet above sea level. Come prepared for warm days and cool nights. Excellent hiking opportunities are available, including a short hike to Jemez Falls or a longer hike along the East Fork Trail, both of which can be accessed from the campground.

Facilities

    The campground contains 51 overnight tent and RV/trailer campsites. There is paved access from the highway and paved internal roads to individual campsites. There are no RV hook-ups at the campground. Drinking water is provided from spigots conveniently located throughout the campground. Vault toilets provide basic sanitation needs. A campground host is on duty during the summer camping season.

Natural Features

    The East Fork Jemez Wild and Scenic River runs close to the campground. The campground is situated on rolling terrain shaded by pines and sunny in open meadows.

Recreation

    Overnight camping, fishing, and hiking are main attractions. Other recreational activities include outdoor photography and nature viewing. The campground is within the heart of the Jemez National Recreation Area.


Activities
•	Day Use Area
•	Fire Lookouts/Cabins Overnight
•	Wildlife Viewing
•	Camping
•	Historic/Cultural Site
•	Biking
</string>
  <string name="camp_info_2">2. Black Canyon ($10 A Night)

For campground inquiries, please call: 505-753-7331
Season Dates
Black Canyon facility is open during the following season(s):
•	May 01, 2020 – October 18, 2020 (Peak Season)
Overview
Black Canyon Campground is in a great location to experience some of the finest mountain scenery the Southwest has to offer. The facility is newly renovated and provides access to a variety of outdoor recreational activities.

Facilities
The campground offers many single and double-family sites, most of which are accessible. Some sites are designated as walk-to sites for tent camping only. A few are available on a first-come, first-served basis. Each site is equipped with a table and campfire ring with grill. Accessible vault toilets and drinking water are provided. The highway to the campground is paved. The campground is adjacent to New Mexicos Hyde State Park, where a dump station is available.

Natural Features
The campground is situated in a forest of pine, aspen and fir trees. A good mix of sun and shade is found throughout the area. Many beautiful views are found in the surrounding forest.

Recreation
Hikers enjoy a pleasant hiking 1.5-mile trail that loops around the campground and into the surrounding forest. Several additional hiking, mountain biking and horseback riding trails are located nearby. The Pecos Wilderness can be accessed eight miles from the campground, with many trails leading to majestic peaks and through valleys, canyons and forested groves. Many recreation opportunities exist along Highway 475, both above and below Black Canyon Campground, including hiking and biking trails and picnic areas. In the winter, the area offers both Nordic and alpine skiing.


Activities
•	Hiking
•	Camping
•	Biking
</string>
  <string name="camp_info_3">3. Clear Creek Campground ($10-$35 A Night)
    Season Dates
Clear Creek Campground (NM) facility is open during the following season(s):
•	May 15, 2020 – September 14, 2020 (Peak Season)
•	September 15, 2020 – September 30, 2020 (First-come, First-served)

Overview
Less than two hours from the city of Albuquerque, Clear Creek Campground offers a cool oasis from the New Mexico heat. Visitors delight in the hiking and fishing opportunities available in the shade of the pine covered Jemez Mountains.

Facilities
Clear Creek Campground includes paved RV pads, fire rings, picnic tables, and vault toilets.

Natural Features
The campground is located amid stunning ponderosa pines in close proximity to Clear Creek.

Recreation
Local streams and the San Gregorio reservoir provide fishing opportunities for anglers, and hikers will delight in the many hiking opportunities in the nearby San Pedro Parks Wilderness.


Activities
•	Hunting
•	Horseback Riding
•	Hiking
•	Fishing
•	Camping
</string>
  <string name="camp_info_4">4. Columbine Campground (NM) ($20 A Night)

Season Dates
Columbine Campground (NM) facility is open during the following season(s):
•	May 22, 2020 – September 13, 2020 (Peak Season)

Overview
Columbine Campground is located between Questa and Red River, New Mexico. The Red River flows past the campground and a trailhead leads into the Columbine-Hondo Wilderness area. Columbine Campground sits at 7,900 feet in elevation.

Facilities
This campground offers 26 single sites, potable water, and vault toilets. Each site is has a fire ring, picnic table, and tent pad. Please note that no water can be filled directly into a trailer, rv, or motorhome anywhere in this campground - the potable water is only for filling containers you bring back to your site.

Natural Features
The campground is composed of two loops. One small loop at the campground entrance, has all open sites and views of the towering mountains. The other is a long loop up the canyon along the fast-flowing Columbine Creek. The campsites in this loop are tucked in among pine, spruce and some aspen providing ample shade and good privacy between campsites.

Recreation
The Columbine Twining hiking trail can be found at the south end of the campground and gives access to 14 miles of hiking trails and leads into the Columbine-Hondo Wilderness area. The Red River runs near the campground and can be accessed near the first loop.


Activities
•	Wildlife Viewing
•	Visitor Center
•	Hiking
•	Fishing
•	Camping
</string>
  <string name="camp_info_5">5. Elephant Rock Campground ($20 A Night)
Season Dates
Elephant Rock Campground facility is open during the following season(s):
•	May 15, 2020 – September 06, 2020 (Non-Peak Season)

Overview
Elephant Rock Campground has excellent fishing access to the well-stocked Red River, nearby Eagle Rock Lake and hiking into the surrounding high country. This campground is close to the highway with plenty of large pine trees. The campground rests at 8,400 feet above sea level.

Facilities
This campground offers 20 single sites, potable water, and vault toilets. Each site has a fire ring, picnic table, and tent pad.

Natural Features
Elephant Rock Campground is a single loop that meanders up a hillside with several sites featuring stone terracing. The campsites are tucked in among a mixture of ponderosa pine, aspen, fir and spruce. The Red River flows near this campground.

Recreation
The nearest hiking trail, Fawn Lakes Trail, is located .3 miles east of Elephant Rock Campground, near Fawn Lakes Campground. This trail meets accessibility guidelines. Elephant Rock offers convenient access to State Rt. 38 and is well situated for day trips on the Enchanted Circle and to the town of Red River. The Red River is across the road from the campground but is not accessible.


Activities
•	Visitor Center
•	Fishing
•	Camping
•	Biking
</string>
  <string name="trail_info_1">Trail Info 1</string>
  <string name="trail_info_2">Trail Info 2</string>
  <string name="trail_info_3">Trail Info 3</string>
  <string name="trail_info_4">Trail Info 4</string>
  <string name="trail_info_5">Trail Info 5</string>
  <string name="trail_info_6">Trail Info 6</string>
  <string name="trail_info_7">Trail Info 7</string>
  <string name="trail_info_8">Trail Info 8</string>
  <string name="trail_info_9">Trail Info 9</string>
  <string name="trail_info_10">Trail Info 10</string>
  <string name="campmaster">Campmaster</string>
  <string name="camping2">View Camp sites</string>
  <string name="community_posts">Community Posts</string>
  <string name="community2">Community Button</string>
  <string name="trailmaster">Trailmaster</string>
  <string name="trails2">ABQ Trails</string>
  <string name="the_grid">the grid</string>
  <string name="to_the_grid">To The Coffee!</string>
  <string name="jemez_national_forrest">Jemez National Forrest</string>
  <string name="black_canyon">Black Canyon</string>
  <string name="clear_creek_campground">Clear Creek Campground</string>
  <string name="columbine_campground">Columbine Campground</string>
  <string name="elephant_rock">Elephant Rock</string>
</resources>
